Guide to the Marjorie Sewell Cautley papers, 1847-1995.
Cautley, Marjorie Sewell papers, 1847-1995.
- Series VII. Miscellaneous
  - Biography of MSC by Nell Walker, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - MSC - Memories of life with her, by Pat Cautley Hill (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Articles featuring MSC, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - American Women Garden Designs (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - MSC - Activities and events recorded by Patt Hill (daughter) (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - MSC - Description of four plans which PCH has one set of slides of the plans the other set of slides with Nell Walker (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Films by MSC in Patt Hill's possession (transferred to DVD-19) (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Robert D. Kohn, Architect NYC, 1870-1953, President of NY Society for Ethical Culture, friend of MSC (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Meuser Park PA, Russell Van Nest Black, Marjorie Sewell's associate, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Meuser Park (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Biographical sketch of Robert Kohn, Architect (worked with MSC) - friends that MSC worked with (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 166)